revmob.com 2017-06-06

# MRI

**Definitions**

" **MRI** ” means the British Virgin Islands Company that is a exclusive agent of Revmob, authorized to operate the Revmob program with worldwide users.

“ **Program** ” means the mobile advertising program you are engaging, also referred to herein as an “advertising network” or solely “network”.

“ **Revmob** ” means the Brazilian company Pubmobile Intermediação de Publicidade e Propaganda Ltda that licensed the program for MRI to operate globally.

“ **Users** ” means any and all participant of the Program, also referred to as “participants”.

**Sources and Use of Data**

In the operation of the Program, MRI and Revmob (or its partners and affiliates) may collect certain information from participants of the advertising network. Such personal or technical information is provided by the Users itself according to the permissions granted by the Users, through automatic collection or the combination of both.

Information received from Users may be collected from the registration data the Users choose to submit or by any other way, such as email or telephone.  In general, every information relied on the questionnaires is valuable for improving the Users' experience and as to customize and improve the Program and the Users' experience.  

Information automatically collected derives from the Users interaction with the Program, apps and/or websites developed by Revmob and/or MRI or other sources, such as tracking the apps and/or websites the Users have used, clicks on advertisements and ads, web browser, indexed data and the connection with the information received and stored.

The personal or technical information from the Users may include but is not limited to:

  * Unique device identifiers such as UDID (not being collected anymore in the newest SDKs), IMEI, MAC Address, and Apple's IDFA
  * Users' ages
  * Country of Users and Users' geo-location
  * Mobile device model of Users
  * Previous installations of advertised application
  * Operating System of Users
  * All of the above data per version of the application and/or website
  * Time when an ad was printed and/or clicked on
  * Time when an advertised app and/or website was installed and/or used

The information collected is used for internal review, advertising, to improve the quality of the Program and technology, to improve security of the network and customize the content and/or display for each individual visitor, and to provide marketing and billing information to Users.  The data may be stored and processed in all the countries.

**Disclosure of Information Collected**

Neither Revmob nor MRI share personal information with third parties for their own interest and use and do not use for contacting Users or telemarketing purposes. Notwithstanding, the personal information may be shared with Revmob or MRI partners, affiliates, advertisers, vendors and other providers and service support. Also, information collected may be disclosed in cases of law accomplishment, court notices, Governmental Authorities requests and to protect the rights of Revmob, MRI and its partners, affiliates and customers. Users who do not want to receive marketing e-mail from Revmob or MRI in the future, should let **both companies** know by writing to the respective email addresses [contact@revmob.com](mailto:contact@bestcoolfunmobileads.com) and contact@mobilerepresentationinternational.com.

**Consents and Profile Preferences**

Users consent and agree that Revmob and MRI may use and share this collected information with their partners, affiliates, and other third-party advertisers. Users who wish to be removed from the database of the Program should send a written request for removal to the respective email addresses [contact@revmob.com](mailto:contact@bestcoolfunmobileads.com) and contact@mobilerepresentationinternational.com and should additionally delete or otherwise stop using and/or completely remove from all Users' mobile devices and systems the Program and all its components.  Notwithstanding the foregoing, Revmob and MRI will comply with duly authorized legal subpoenas from law enforcement or other lawful governmental request seeking information.

Revmob and MRI Online Account Holders should edit their online profile to correct any inaccurate information and to keep the information current, complete and accurate. If there are further issues with the accuracy of information, consumers may contact Revmob and MRI at the addresses above for further resolution. Account Holders are responsible for all activity undertaken through their account or password, and for maintaining the security of their password and other personal information. Account holders are not permitted to allow others to use their account or password assigned to them without the written permission of Revmob and MRI.

**Security of Users' Data**

With respect to security: the Program contains appropriate security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that it has collected from Users.  Notwithstanding the foregoing, Revmob and MRI make no warranty regarding security or protection of personal or other data.

**Effectiveness and term of this Policy**

This Privacy Policy may be changed at any time at the discretion of Revmob and/or MRI and encompasses the information collected during the effective period. Further amendments to the Privacy Policy will be notified by posting an announcement on your account so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.

December 1st, 2016
